ps3hax.net 2009-02-14

# PS3HaX Network - PS3 Hacks

PS3HaX Network has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.ps3hax.net

Information Automatically Logged: We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The IP is simply stored for security purposes, such as a DOS attack. Your IP is not used for any other purposes. 

Advertisers: We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. PS3HaX Network does not use cookies unless you are a registered member on this website, and cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company; we do not have access to this information. 

Personal Information: This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. However, at times, we may run certain sweepstakes for which filling out a survey is required. This information may be used to target our advertisements. Individual responses are not kept on file, and none of this information is sold to anyone outside the site. At no time is personal information collected without explicit consent. 

External Links: This site contains links to other sites. PS3HaX Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Public Forums: This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. All information on this website is for educational purposes only. 

Security: This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

Contacting the Web Site: If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: admin@dootinc.com
